<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AboutMeApp</string>
    <string name="name_txt">Bramdont Garcia</string>
    <string name="yellow_Star">Yellow Star</string>
    <string name="bio_txt">A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter. A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter. A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter. A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter. A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter. A biography, or simply bio, is a detailed description of a persons life. It involves more than just the basic facts like education, work, relationships, and death; it portrays a persons experience of these life events. Unlike a profile or curriculum vitae (resume), a biography presents a subjects life story, highlighting various aspects of his or her life, including intimate details of experience, and may include an analysis of the subjects personality. Biographical works are usually non-fiction, but fiction can also be used to portray a persons life. One in-depth form of biographical coverage is called legacy writing. Works in diverse media, from literature to film, form the genre known as biography. An authorized biography is written with the permission, cooperation, and at times, participation of a subject or a subjects heirs. An autobiography is written by the person himself or herself, sometimes with the assistance of a collaborator or ghostwriter.</string>
</resources>
